text2speech.org 2015-12-31

# Privacy - Text2speech.org

## PRIVACY POLICY

### Personal Data Collected by us

In general, we collect only your IP address along with the dates and times of access, as this not avoidable due to the technical workings of a webserver. We do not link this information to any personally identifiable information. 

If you send us a donation through PayPal, we will get your personal data about your PayPal account but we do not store it.   
If you send us a letter via our contact form, we do not store your name and email address.   
We use the email address only to communicate with you. We will never share or resell your email address. 

### Storage of User Files and generated Data

All submitted files or inputs as well as the converted output are deleted automatically after half an hour. No backups are made and only employees of t-reinhardt.ch are able to access your files. We keep the files for the sole purpose for giving you enough time to download them. We do not look at the files or mine any data from them. 

### How we use Cookies

We use cookies solely for functional purposes, without storing any user information. For example, we store information like selected input options to increase the usability of our site. We do not use cookies to track you. 

However, Google Analytics, Google DoubleClick, and Google Adsense, which we are using on this site, do use cookies on our site to help analyse the web traffic or determine targeted advertisements based on your preferences, your visit on our sites and other sites on the internet. To opt out of Google’s use of cookies, please visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy. If you prefer not to use cookies at all, we recommend adjusting your browser settings accordingly. 

## TERMS OF SERVICE

### Responsiblities for any Damages or Troubles

We are working hard to ensure that the services we offer are free of errors but we cannot guarantee that. As a user of this service you agree that t-reinhardt.ch will not be held responsible for any failure or error. 

### Copyright Issues

Do not use our services and intellectual property for any form of infringement. 

## DATE OF MODIFICATION

2015-06-21  
Changes to this terms and conditions will be indicated by a change of this page date of modification.
